

# RIFQI FINALDY

+6285871097993 | rifqifinaldy@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/rifqi-finaldy/ | https://porto-rifqi-fv2.vercel.app/

Bandung

Experienced Frontend Developer (2-3 Years) in developing and driving projects forward from concept into production ready. Currently addicted to React and enthusiast with Javascript. Easily inspired and prefer to keep learning and continue to challenging myself as "Skills can be taught and Personality is inherent".

## **Work Experiences**

#### PT. MNC Media Baru (Buddyku) - Jakarta

Feb 2023 - May 2023

#### Frontend Developer

https://buddyku.com/

- Maintained and developed 1-3 feature in every sprint on legacy web app code.
- Integrated the web app with the third party application.
- · Rewrote HTML to meet industry and company standard for SEO and Accessibility.
- Utilized HTML, CSS and JS to create responsive and pixel perfect landing pages.
- Collaborated with Product, Design, and Backend team to create fully functional feature.

### PT. Orde Digital Intelektual (Ordent) - Bandung

Jun 2022 - Feb 2023

#### Frontend Developer

https://ordent.co/

- · Developed and Optimized 5 project for maximum speed and scalability simultaneously.
- Collaborated with System Analyst, Designer and Backend Team in analyzing concepts based on the user requirement.
- Improved security on the client side code to prevent host injection.
- · Contributed in UAT, SIT & Pentest of the project's.

#### PT. Transformasi Data Indonesia (Socketspace) - Cimahi

Apr 2021 - Apr 2022

### Frontend Developer

https://socketspace.com/

- Delivered 7 projects of all sizes from scratch.
- Assisted in creating reusable code, components, and library for future use.
- Validated 100% of user input before submitting to the backend.
- · Incorporated visual design projects into functional UI.
- · Participated in the initial wave of developers learning to hone the initial fundamental

#### CV. Passion IT - Bandung

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

Frontend Developer (Intern)

- · Design & Build Dynamic Company Profile Website
- Translate UI/UX into fully functional Code

## **Education Level**

## National Institute of Technology Bandung - Bandung

Sep 2015 - Feb 2020

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science, 3.28/4.00

· Participated in ICGTD Itenas as presenter

# Organisational Experience

**HMIF Itenas - Bandung** 

Jan 2016 - Jan 2019

Head of Art Division

- Contributed & Supporting HMIF Itenas event as a performer
- · Muster all HMIF Itenas colleagues who had interest in art & creativity

# **Skills**

- Frontend Development: HTML, CSS, SCSS/SASS, Javascript, React JS, Redux, EJS, Vue JS, Nuxt, Vuex, Pinia, Tailwind Css, Bootsrap, Material UI, AJAX, Jquery, Styled Component
- Graphic Design & UI/UX: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Frammer Motion, Adobe Premier, Balsamiq
- · Others: Navicat, Monggo DB, Node JS, Express, Contentful